bonetown.com 2010-03-06

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Information we collect on the BoneTown website may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways:

Deliver merchandise that you purchase online   
Register you as a member of BoneTown.com   
Bill your credit card for your purchases   
Confirm your shopping orders   
Respond to your customer service inquiries or requests

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We will share personal customer information only with our trusted service providers and contractors for the limited purposes of fulfilling customer orders; communicating to customers; providing customer service; and completing credit card transactions.

Aside from the purposes described above, we will never share your personal information with any other third parties unless we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required by law.

Registering as a BoneTown.com customer lets us provide a better shopping experience for you and allows you to make purchases more conveniently, without having to re-enter your payment and shipping information each time you make a purchase on our site.

As a registered user, you can modify your personal information anytime.

Do not share your BoneTown.com password with anyone.

If you choose to receive them, we may periodically send you email messages with news about BoneTown and special promotions. You can choose to stop receiving this email at any time.

The only email messages you will receive from us when you elect not to receive informational emails will be to confirm any purchases you make on our site, let you know your order has been shipped, respond to your Support inquiries and to answer any other questions you may have about our site. We may also need to send operational emails to inform you of any changes to our site that might affect your personal information, or to announce product recalls.

BoneTown.com automatically collects and stores the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access one of our sites; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to our site, address our users' preferences and to attract new users, and, in some instances, to properly credit third-parties who refer users to our site.

DWC Software may during the course of your visit to our site, store "cookies" on your computer. Cookies are small pieces of information that an internet website can put on your computer to help track information about your visit. You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer by adjusting the preferences of your web browser.

The security of your personal information is very important to us. In our efforts to protect your online transactions, we use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If your browser is capable of SSL (and most are), your personal information will be automatically encrypted, or encoded, before it is sent over the Internet.

Ultimately, your personal information is protected by the password you created when you registered for an account at BoneTown.com (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. The confidentiality of your password is your responsibility to protect. You may change it anytime. Log in with your username and password, then click "Change Password" and enter a new password.
